<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tour | CM Foundation</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu1cdf2fb96ab495858a3f8119d18c4363_92516_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Tour</title>
      <link>https://example.com/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/musici/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/musici/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here there are names of students with maybe a picture and some stories. Potentially a list of all students that received funding (AVG?).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/sponsoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/sponsoring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can you do to help us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lovers contribute financial support for (international) projects, world-renowned masterclasses, instrument maintenance and &amp;lsquo;first-aid kits&amp;rsquo; for students in need.
You can help in numerous ways, as you can do a donation of your choice or contribute in other ways than with financial support. It is also possible to be a Platinum, Gold or Silver Lover. Naturally, those wonderful contributions do not go unrewarded. These are unique opportunities, to meet talented musicians at an early stage, follow them and witness their development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platinum: 5000 euro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet the artists
Learn more during masterclasses, or simply observe and enjoy
Free tickets for concerts, or the opportunity to pre-order
Exclusive Lovers Concert
VIP experience during selected concerts
Advertising opportunities
Gold: 2500 euro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more during masterclasses, or simply observe and enjoy
Free tickets for concerts, or the opportunity to pre-order
Exclusive Lovers Concert
VIP experience during selected concerts
Silver: 1000 euro (alumni discount: 500 euro)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more during masterclasses, or simply observe and enjoy
Free tickets for concerts, or the opportunity to pre-order
Exclusive Lovers Concert
You can donate a free amount to:
CMF Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation
IBAN: NL77RABO0191906476
BIC: RABONL2U&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to become a Platinum, Gold or Silver Lovers, contact us, via &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:communicatie.conservatorium@zuyd.nl&#34;&gt;communicatie.conservatorium@zuyd.nl&lt;/a&gt;
Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation is an ANBI-foundation (Algemeen Nut Beogende Instelling).
Donating is tax-refundable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Maastricht Academy of Music has set up the Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation (CMF) along with a number of music lovers in order to raise funds to support talented students at the Academy who find themselves in financial difficulty. Finances The funds available to the CMF mean that it can provide a limited number of talented students with financial aid to help them offset their study costs, the purchase of an instrument, or attendance at master classes and competitions in the Netherlands and abroad. Aid is only provided, of course, if the students concerned do not already have sufficient financial resources. Applications and selection Students who wish to apply for financial aid from the CMF must fill in the appropriate application form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Application is possible twice a year:
First round: You can apply from August till mid-November. You will receive the result (and possible scholarship) in January.
Second round: You can apply from January till mid-April. You will receive the result (and possible scholarship) after October 1st of the following academic year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply Now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/bestuur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/about/bestuur/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antoine Huenges Wajer (Chair)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vincent Kusters (Secretary)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ton Bemelmans (Treasurer)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mette Laugs (Member)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Peter Steijvers (Member)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edouard Rasquin (Member)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Slangen (Member)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/jaarrekening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/about/jaarrekening/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation is an ANBI-foundation (Algemeen Nut Beogende Instelling). Donating is tax-refundable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the Financial Statements:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaarrekening</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/about/partners/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who are we?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/about/goals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation is a community of music lovers who stimulate the development of innovation in music. The basis for this lies in the education of talented students from the Classical, Jazz and Music in Education departments at Conservatorium Maastricht.
Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation strives to promote a musical climate without borders, giving the students ample opportunity to develop as performers/creators, teachers, researchers, and/or entrepreneurs. this allows them to contribute to the international world of music and to society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why?
Being able to study and develop your talents is a wonderful opportunity. An opportunity which many of us have had, but which is not available to everyone, or not available to the same extent. That also applies to musicians. As well as requiring talent, studying at a conservatoire has specific financial implications. Performing requires travel, instruments need to be purchased and maintained, and special masterclasses attended.
In order to support young talented musicians, Conservatorium Maastricht has set up the Conservatorium Maastricht Foundation (CMF). Thanks to the warm contributions from sympathisers, this foundation can help students from around the world to fund their studies. These donations have a huge impact. It is a quality incentive that allows students to concentrate fully on their studies and eventually excel in their profession even more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Goals
Musicians are ambitious, focused, creative and studious people. While immersed in their studies, many find themselves struggling with financial dificulties. Whether this is due to budget cuts in the music sector or personal issues, it inevitably means they are unable to attend certain crucial programmes. We have set ourselves the following goals to help remedy this situation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enhance the environment at Conservatorium Maastricht; enable and support education to boost quality.
Build a strong community of alumni and provide life-long learning opportunities.
Build a strong community of lovers with a passion for music, recognizing the importance of fundraising.
Within the music community (students and teachers), we want to foster initiative, talent and innovation through financial aid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
